{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511679090","data":{"timestamp":" 947511679090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 3c25fbac-a4cd-4c43-a2ed-9d56481b05b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SA"," userResponse":" SA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511680172","data":{"timestamp":" 947511680171"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 3c25fbac-a4cd-4c43-a2ed-9d56481b05b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SA"," userResponse":" SA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511683559","data":{"timestamp":" 947511683558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 3c25fbac-a4cd-4c43-a2ed-9d56481b05b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" se"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SE"," userResponse":" SE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511684627","data":{"timestamp":" 947511684626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 3c25fbac-a4cd-4c43-a2ed-9d56481b05b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" se"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SE"," userResponse":" SE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511687643","data":{"timestamp":" 947511687642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 3c25fbac-a4cd-4c43-a2ed-9d56481b05b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" si"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511688696","data":{"timestamp":" 947511688696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 3c25fbac-a4cd-4c43-a2ed-9d56481b05b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" si"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511692864","data":{"timestamp":" 947511692864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 3c25fbac-a4cd-4c43-a2ed-9d56481b05b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" so"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SO"," userResponse":" SO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511693932","data":{"timestamp":" 947511693932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 3c25fbac-a4cd-4c43-a2ed-9d56481b05b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" so"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SO"," userResponse":" SO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511697160","data":{"timestamp":" 947511697160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 3c25fbac-a4cd-4c43-a2ed-9d56481b05b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" su"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SU"," userResponse":" SU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511698233","data":{"timestamp":" 947511698232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 3c25fbac-a4cd-4c43-a2ed-9d56481b05b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" su"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SU"," userResponse":" SU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511701483","data":{"timestamp":" 947511701482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 3c25fbac-a4cd-4c43-a2ed-9d56481b05b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" su"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511701608","data":{"timestamp":" 947511701608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 3c25fbac-a4cd-4c43-a2ed-9d56481b05b4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.sa..su.asc.lc.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" su"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SU"," userResponse":" SU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511725648","data":{"timestamp":" 947511725648"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" b3e7a66a-3dca-4ecb-813d-5a82d3ed715d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ga_pe-ti-ga"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511730675","data":{"timestamp":" 947511730675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" b3e7a66a-3dca-4ecb-813d-5a82d3ed715d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ze_ku-wa-ze"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ze"," userResponse":" ze"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511737006","data":{"timestamp":" 947511737006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" b3e7a66a-3dca-4ecb-813d-5a82d3ed715d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_de_pe-ha-de"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" de"," userResponse":" de"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511742280","data":{"timestamp":" 947511742279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" b3e7a66a-3dca-4ecb-813d-5a82d3ed715d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ho_ho-sa-mu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ho"," userResponse":" ho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511747904","data":{"timestamp":" 947511747904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" b3e7a66a-3dca-4ecb-813d-5a82d3ed715d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_jo_di-jo-wi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" jo"," userResponse":" jo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511753734","data":{"timestamp":" 947511753733"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" b3e7a66a-3dca-4ecb-813d-5a82d3ed715d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pi_pi-zo-we"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pi"," userResponse":" pi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511763125","data":{"timestamp":" 947511763125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" b3e7a66a-3dca-4ecb-813d-5a82d3ed715d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_pu_du-pu-ta"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511768181","data":{"timestamp":" 947511768181"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" b3e7a66a-3dca-4ecb-813d-5a82d3ed715d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ji_je-ji-si"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ji"," userResponse":" ji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511774759","data":{"timestamp":" 947511774759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" b3e7a66a-3dca-4ecb-813d-5a82d3ed715d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_po_po-no-da"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" po"," userResponse":" po"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511779779","data":{"timestamp":" 947511779779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" b3e7a66a-3dca-4ecb-813d-5a82d3ed715d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" wu"," userResponse":" wu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511785571","data":{"timestamp":" 947511785569"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" b3e7a66a-3dca-4ecb-813d-5a82d3ed715d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_2ch..2ch.syl.rand.all.stat.show.47__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_wu_zo-wu-ja"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511807209","data":{"timestamp":" 947511807208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511807603","data":{"timestamp":" 947511807602"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511807847","data":{"timestamp":" 947511807846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511808170","data":{"timestamp":" 947511808169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511808413","data":{"timestamp":" 947511808413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511811956","data":{"timestamp":" 947511811955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511812261","data":{"timestamp":" 947511812261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511813175","data":{"timestamp":" 947511813174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511813609","data":{"timestamp":" 947511813608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511816537","data":{"timestamp":" 947511816537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511816830","data":{"timestamp":" 947511816829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511817685","data":{"timestamp":" 947511817685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511818361","data":{"timestamp":" 947511818361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511819110","data":{"timestamp":" 947511819110"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511819452","data":{"timestamp":" 947511819451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511819741","data":{"timestamp":" 947511819741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511820062","data":{"timestamp":" 947511820062"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511820336","data":{"timestamp":" 947511820335"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511824060","data":{"timestamp":" 947511824060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511824454","data":{"timestamp":" 947511824453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511824698","data":{"timestamp":" 947511824697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511825025","data":{"timestamp":" 947511825025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511825271","data":{"timestamp":" 947511825270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511828757","data":{"timestamp":" 947511828757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511829059","data":{"timestamp":" 947511829059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511829975","data":{"timestamp":" 947511829974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511830408","data":{"timestamp":" 947511830407"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511833409","data":{"timestamp":" 947511833409"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511833703","data":{"timestamp":" 947511833702"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511834561","data":{"timestamp":" 947511834560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511835245","data":{"timestamp":" 947511835244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511835996","data":{"timestamp":" 947511835995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511836333","data":{"timestamp":" 947511836333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511836623","data":{"timestamp":" 947511836622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511836946","data":{"timestamp":" 947511836946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511837219","data":{"timestamp":" 947511837218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511840654","data":{"timestamp":" 947511840651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511840777","data":{"timestamp":" 947511840777"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 96933fb4-7764-46af-88b5-e24b6df5c5bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511859588","data":{"timestamp":" 947511859588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 2cbc8dac-e7f6-461e-bce4-e61a95dbde7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ng'u-fo-ta"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511863884","data":{"timestamp":" 947511863884"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 2cbc8dac-e7f6-461e-bce4-e61a95dbde7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-pe-ngu"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511869251","data":{"timestamp":" 947511869250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 2cbc8dac-e7f6-461e-bce4-e61a95dbde7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_do-ta-mo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511874757","data":{"timestamp":" 947511874757"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 2cbc8dac-e7f6-461e-bce4-e61a95dbde7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_si-ta-shu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511881030","data":{"timestamp":" 947511881030"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 2cbc8dac-e7f6-461e-bce4-e61a95dbde7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ng'i-ta-mwa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511885743","data":{"timestamp":" 947511885743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 2cbc8dac-e7f6-461e-bce4-e61a95dbde7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ku-ta-nyi"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511893515","data":{"timestamp":" 947511893514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 2cbc8dac-e7f6-461e-bce4-e61a95dbde7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_mwu-ta-shi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511899379","data":{"timestamp":" 947511899379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 2cbc8dac-e7f6-461e-bce4-e61a95dbde7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ti-ta-mwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511904987","data":{"timestamp":" 947511904987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 2cbc8dac-e7f6-461e-bce4-e61a95dbde7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_mche-ta-mpi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511913152","data":{"timestamp":" 947511913152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 2cbc8dac-e7f6-461e-bce4-e61a95dbde7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-vyi-ve"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511918955","data":{"timestamp":" 947511918955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 2cbc8dac-e7f6-461e-bce4-e61a95dbde7c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.show.11"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-vyi-ve"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511945107","data":{"timestamp":" 947511945107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" ea9a3844-4f90-4532-9309-ff931131cdbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-ng'a-tha"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511958818","data":{"timestamp":" 947511958817"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" ea9a3844-4f90-4532-9309-ff931131cdbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_mja-ta-mcha"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511964987","data":{"timestamp":" 947511964987"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" ea9a3844-4f90-4532-9309-ff931131cdbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-nga-va"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511971796","data":{"timestamp":" 947511971796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" ea9a3844-4f90-4532-9309-ff931131cdbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_tha-msta-ta"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511977958","data":{"timestamp":" 947511977958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" ea9a3844-4f90-4532-9309-ff931131cdbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ba-ta-mna"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511983787","data":{"timestamp":" 947511983787"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" ea9a3844-4f90-4532-9309-ff931131cdbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-mfa-mpa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947511991252","data":{"timestamp":" 947511991252"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" ea9a3844-4f90-4532-9309-ff931131cdbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_msa-ta-mta"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512000457","data":{"timestamp":" 947512000457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" ea9a3844-4f90-4532-9309-ff931131cdbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-mpa-sa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512014954","data":{"timestamp":" 947512014954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" ea9a3844-4f90-4532-9309-ff931131cdbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_nga-ja-ta"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512062082","data":{"timestamp":" 947512062082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" ea9a3844-4f90-4532-9309-ff931131cdbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-mka-nda"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512067869","data":{"timestamp":" 947512067868"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" ea9a3844-4f90-4532-9309-ff931131cdbb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.sim.stat.show.12"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-mka-nda"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512114100","data":{"timestamp":" 947512114100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 919a29d1-231c-456f-9ca6-9691f674dad7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_pi-be-ta"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512118743","data":{"timestamp":" 947512118743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 919a29d1-231c-456f-9ca6-9691f674dad7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_mre-ma-ta"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512123514","data":{"timestamp":" 947512123514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 919a29d1-231c-456f-9ca6-9691f674dad7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_bu-ta-mte"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512127903","data":{"timestamp":" 947512127903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 919a29d1-231c-456f-9ca6-9691f674dad7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_je-ta-do"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" je"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512133193","data":{"timestamp":" 947512133193"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 919a29d1-231c-456f-9ca6-9691f674dad7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_je-ta-do"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512137990","data":{"timestamp":" 947512137990"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 919a29d1-231c-456f-9ca6-9691f674dad7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-mcho-bo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512143077","data":{"timestamp":" 947512143077"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 919a29d1-231c-456f-9ca6-9691f674dad7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_pe-ta-mju"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512148054","data":{"timestamp":" 947512148053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 919a29d1-231c-456f-9ca6-9691f674dad7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-mla-nya"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512158519","data":{"timestamp":" 947512158519"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 919a29d1-231c-456f-9ca6-9691f674dad7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_ta-mwu-vyo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512166523","data":{"timestamp":" 947512166523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 919a29d1-231c-456f-9ca6-9691f674dad7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_pa-ta-dha"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512173528","data":{"timestamp":" 947512173528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 919a29d1-231c-456f-9ca6-9691f674dad7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_mre-cha-ta"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ta"," userResponse":" ta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512179307","data":{"timestamp":" 947512179306"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 919a29d1-231c-456f-9ca6-9691f674dad7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_ta..ta.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ta_mre-cha-ta"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512202935","data":{"timestamp":" 947512202934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 33c9fe24-d0d4-49df-a484-6f88ca1f4bd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TA"," userResponse":" TA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512205824","data":{"timestamp":" 947512205823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 33c9fe24-d0d4-49df-a484-6f88ca1f4bd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512207396","data":{"timestamp":" 947512207396"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 33c9fe24-d0d4-49df-a484-6f88ca1f4bd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" te"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TE"," userResponse":" TE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512210563","data":{"timestamp":" 947512210562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 33c9fe24-d0d4-49df-a484-6f88ca1f4bd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" te"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512212190","data":{"timestamp":" 947512212189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 33c9fe24-d0d4-49df-a484-6f88ca1f4bd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TI"," userResponse":" TI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512215097","data":{"timestamp":" 947512215097"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 33c9fe24-d0d4-49df-a484-6f88ca1f4bd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512216718","data":{"timestamp":" 947512216717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 33c9fe24-d0d4-49df-a484-6f88ca1f4bd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" to"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TO"," userResponse":" TO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512219675","data":{"timestamp":" 947512219674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 33c9fe24-d0d4-49df-a484-6f88ca1f4bd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" to"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512221279","data":{"timestamp":" 947512221278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 33c9fe24-d0d4-49df-a484-6f88ca1f4bd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512224200","data":{"timestamp":" 947512224200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 33c9fe24-d0d4-49df-a484-6f88ca1f4bd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512226228","data":{"timestamp":" 947512226227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 33c9fe24-d0d4-49df-a484-6f88ca1f4bd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" tu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512226479","data":{"timestamp":" 947512226479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 33c9fe24-d0d4-49df-a484-6f88ca1f4bd8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512241898","data":{"timestamp":" 947512241897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 697f7b75-87c4-464b-b5af-0ae67a600640"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TA"," userResponse":" TA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512244884","data":{"timestamp":" 947512244883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 697f7b75-87c4-464b-b5af-0ae67a600640"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TA"," userResponse":" TA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512246455","data":{"timestamp":" 947512246455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 697f7b75-87c4-464b-b5af-0ae67a600640"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" te"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TE"," userResponse":" TE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512249675","data":{"timestamp":" 947512249675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 697f7b75-87c4-464b-b5af-0ae67a600640"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" te"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512251269","data":{"timestamp":" 947512251269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 697f7b75-87c4-464b-b5af-0ae67a600640"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TI"," userResponse":" TI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512254823","data":{"timestamp":" 947512254823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 697f7b75-87c4-464b-b5af-0ae67a600640"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512256431","data":{"timestamp":" 947512256430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 697f7b75-87c4-464b-b5af-0ae67a600640"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" to"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TO"," userResponse":" TO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512259271","data":{"timestamp":" 947512259270"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 697f7b75-87c4-464b-b5af-0ae67a600640"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" to"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512260870","data":{"timestamp":" 947512260870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 697f7b75-87c4-464b-b5af-0ae67a600640"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512264187","data":{"timestamp":" 947512264186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 697f7b75-87c4-464b-b5af-0ae67a600640"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512266221","data":{"timestamp":" 947512266219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 697f7b75-87c4-464b-b5af-0ae67a600640"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" tu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512266364","data":{"timestamp":" 947512266363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 697f7b75-87c4-464b-b5af-0ae67a600640"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512283622","data":{"timestamp":" 947512283622"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 1dc7ae4d-dc3f-4ca1-a734-f0c282940e8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512284245","data":{"timestamp":" 947512284244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 1dc7ae4d-dc3f-4ca1-a734-f0c282940e8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512284334","data":{"timestamp":" 947512284334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 1dc7ae4d-dc3f-4ca1-a734-f0c282940e8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512284415","data":{"timestamp":" 947512284415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 1dc7ae4d-dc3f-4ca1-a734-f0c282940e8d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512313932","data":{"timestamp":" 947512313930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 8cf1d912-2857-443e-9674-daab321d612e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TA"," userResponse":" TA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512314997","data":{"timestamp":" 947512314996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 8cf1d912-2857-443e-9674-daab321d612e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TA"," userResponse":" TA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512317654","data":{"timestamp":" 947512317653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 8cf1d912-2857-443e-9674-daab321d612e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" te"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TE"," userResponse":" TE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512317723","data":{"timestamp":" 947512317722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 8cf1d912-2857-443e-9674-daab321d612e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" te"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512318747","data":{"timestamp":" 947512318746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 8cf1d912-2857-443e-9674-daab321d612e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TI"," userResponse":" TI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512321027","data":{"timestamp":" 947512321026"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 8cf1d912-2857-443e-9674-daab321d612e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TI"," userResponse":" TI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512327059","data":{"timestamp":" 947512327059"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 8cf1d912-2857-443e-9674-daab321d612e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" to"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TO"," userResponse":" TO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512328129","data":{"timestamp":" 947512328129"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 8cf1d912-2857-443e-9674-daab321d612e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" to"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TO"," userResponse":" TO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512332209","data":{"timestamp":" 947512332209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 8cf1d912-2857-443e-9674-daab321d612e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512333254","data":{"timestamp":" 947512333254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 8cf1d912-2857-443e-9674-daab321d612e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512336505","data":{"timestamp":" 947512336504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 8cf1d912-2857-443e-9674-daab321d612e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" tu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947512336642","data":{"timestamp":" 947512336642"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_164106"," gameId":" 8cf1d912-2857-443e-9674-daab321d612e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__syl.ta..tu.asc.lc.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}